Guide to the Walter Lowenfels Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings of Others, 1941-1976; Series III; 6; (14 boxes)
  - Writings by Author, 1941-1976
    - Durem, Ray, undated (Box 147, Folder 2295)
    - Engles, Frederick, undated (Box 147, Folder 2296)
    - Enslin, Ted, undated (Box 147, Folder 2297)
    - Evans, Mari, undated (Box 147, Folder 2298)
    - Fast, Howard, undated (Box 147, Folder 2299)
    - Ferrini, Vincent, undated (Box 147, Folder 2300)
    - Ficowski, Jerzy, undated (Box 147, Folder 2301)
    - Field, Edward, undated (Box 147, Folder 2302)
    - Florance, Edward, undated (Box 147, Folder 2303)
    - Flynn, E. G., undated (Box 147, Folder 2304)
    - Ford, Edsel, 1964 May 21 (Box 147, Folder 2305)
    - Forrey, Robert, undated (Box 147, Folder 2306)
    - Forshay, Richard Don, 1968 (Box 147, Folder 2307)
    - Foster, Donn, undated (Box 147, Folder 2308)
    - Fowler, Gene, undated (Box 147, Folder 2309)
    - Frumkin, Gene, undated (Box 147, Folder 2310)
    - Galt, Lisa, undated (Box 147, Folder 2311)
    - Garneau, Sylvan, undated (Box 147, Folder 2312)
    - Geddes, Jeff, undated (Box 147, Folder 2313)
    - Geismar, Maxwell, undated (Box 147, Folder 2314)
    - Georgakas, Dan. "And all the living things their children", 1970 (Box 147, Folder 2315)
    - George, Wilton A., undated (Box 147, Folder 2316)
    - Gershgoren, Estelle, undated (Box 147, Folder 2317)
    - Gershgoren, Sid, undated (Box 147, Folder 2318)
    - Gibson, Morgan, 1968, undated (Box 147, Folder 2319)
    - Gill, John, 1966, undated (Box 147, Folder 2320)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, undated (Box 147, Folder 2321)
    - Gledhill, Sabrina, 1968, undated (Box 147, Folder 2322)
    - Glen, Emilie, undated (Box 147, Folder 2323)
    - Goode, Jene Tracy, undated (Box 147, Folder 2324)
    - Goodman, Miriam, undated (Box 147, Folder 2325)
    - Goodman, R., undated (Box 147, Folder 2326)
    - Goytisolo, Jose Augustin, undated (Box 147, Folder 2327)
    - Graham, Le, undated (Box 147, Folder 2328)
    - Graves, Robert, undated (Box 147, Folder 2329)
    - Greer, Carolyn, undated (Box 147, Folder 2330)
    - Grochowiak, Stanislaw, undated (Box 147, Folder 2331)
    - Gross, Ronald, undated (Box 147, Folder 2332)
    - Grundberg, Andy, 1969 May (Box 147, Folder 2333)
    - Guillevic, undated (Box 147, Folder 2334)
    - Gwynn, Donald Grafton, undated (Box 147, Folder 2335)
    - Hall, Steven, undated (Box 148, Folder 2336)
    - Hall, Tim, undated (Box 148, Folder 2337)
    - Harmon, William. Civic Choruses, typescript and Wesleyan, galley proof, 1971, undated (Box 148, Folder 2338-2339)
    - Harper, Michael S., undated (Box 148, Folder 2340)
    - Harris, Emily Katharine, undated (Box 148, Folder 2341)
    - Harris, Marguerite, undated (Box 148, Folder 2342)
    - Harrison, Pat, undated (Box 148, Folder 2343)
    - Harvey, Louise, 1962, undated (Box 148, Folder 2344)
    - Hays, Lee, undated (Box 148, Folder 2345)
    - Hebald, Carol, undated (Box 148, Folder 2346)
    - Hedley, Leslie Woolf, undated (Box 148, Folder 2347)
    - Henderson, David, 1965, undated (Box 148, Folder 2348)
    - Herreshoff, David, 1966-1968, undated (Box 148, Folder 2349)
    - Hertel, Francois, undated (Box 148, Folder 2350)
    - Hikmet, undated (Box 148, Folder 2351)
    - Hill, Hyacinthe, undated (Box 148, Folder 2352)
    - Himmersky, Krassen, undated (Box 148, Folder 2353)
    - Hirshcliffe, Barbara, undated (Box 148, Folder 2354)
    - Hirschman, Jack, undated (Box 148, Folder 2355)
    - Hoague, Lucy B., 1972 February (Box 148, Folder 2356)
    - Hoàng, Trung Thông, undated (Box 148, Folder 2357)
    - Holmes, R. Ernest, undated (Box 148, Folder 2358)
    - Hopper, Paul, undated (Box 148, Folder 2359)
    - Hosein, Clyde, undated (Box 148, Folder 2360)
    - Howard, Ben, undated (Box 148, Folder 2361)
    - Howery, Jack, undated (Box 148, Folder 2362)
    - Hughes, Langston, undated (Box 148, Folder 2363)
    - Huidobro, Vincente, undated (Box 148, Folder 2364)
    - Humboldt, Charles, undated (Box 148, Folder 2365)
    - Ignatow, David, undated (Box 148, Folder 2366-2367)
    - Inez, Colette, 1973, undated (Box 148, Folder 2368)
    - Inman, Will, 1965-1967, undated (Box 148, Folder 2369)
    - Isaac, Gita, undated (Box 148, Folder 2370)
    - Jackmon, Marvin, undated (Box 149, Folder 2371)
    - Jackson, Gerald, 1971, undated (Box 149, Folder 2372)
    - Jacobs, George, 1966 (Box 149, Folder 2373)
    - Jacobs, Scott, 1968, undated (Box 149, Folder 2374)
    - James, William, undated (Box 149, Folder 2375)
    - Jamison, Don, undated (Box 149, Folder 2376)
    - Jerome, V. J., undated (Box 149, Folder 2377)
    - Johnson, Joe, undated (Box 149, Folder 2378)
    - Johnson, Kay, undated (Box 149, Folder 2379)
    - Johnson, T., undated (Box 149, Folder 2380)
    - Jones, Alice H., undated (Box 149, Folder 2381)
    - Jones, Leroi
      See Baraka, Imamu Amiri and Larry Neal. Black Fire. Galley proofs; Stored in Oversize, Box 174, Folder 2990
    - Jordan, June, 1970 (Box 149, Folder 2382)
    - Juergensen, Hans, 1974, undated (Box 149, Folder 2383)
    - Juergensen, Ilse, undated (Box 149, Folder 2384)
    - Juin, Hubert, undated (Box 149, Folder 2385)
    - Kahn, Albert E., undated (Box 149, Folder 2386)
    - Kaplan, Jonathan, 1967-1968, undated (Box 149, Folder 2387)
    - Katz, Gwen, undated (Box 149, Folder 2388)
    - Katzman, Allen, undated (Box 149, Folder 2389)
    - Kaufman, Bob, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 2390)
    - Keidon, Seymour, undated (Box 149, Folder 2391)
    - Keith, William, undated (Box 149, Folder 2392)
    - Kelly, Robert, undated (Box 149, Folder 2393)
    - Kenin, Millea, 1968, undated (Box 149, Folder 2394)
    - Kgositsile, Keorapetse, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 2395)
    - Khimirsky, Krassin, undated (Box 149, Folder 2396)
    - Kinnell, Galway, undated (Box 149, Folder 2397)
    - Knight, Ethridge, undated (Box 149, Folder 2398)
    - Knott, Bill, 1968 (Box 149, Folder 2399)
    - Kohut, Joel, undated (Box 149, Folder 2400)
    - Koontz, Dean, undated (Box 149, Folder 2401)
    - Kumin, Maxine, undated (Box 149, Folder 2402)
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, 1964, undated (Box 149, Folder 2403)
    - Kurtz, Aaron, undated (Box 149, Folder 2404)
    - Lakin, R. D., undated (Box 149, Folder 2405)
    - Lally, Michael, undated (Box 149, Folder 2406)
    - Larsen, Carl, undated (Box 149, Folder 2407)
    - Laster, Clara, undated (Box 149, Folder 2408)
    - Lawson, Sue, undated (Box 149, Folder 2409)
    - Lee, Bert, undated (Box 149, Folder 2410)
    - Lee, Don L., 1968, undated (Box 149, Folder 2411)
    - Lehman, John, 1955 (Box 149, Folder 2412)
    - Leopold, Rose Kagan, undated (Box 149, Folder 2413)
    - Lesley, Catherine, undated (Box 149, Folder 2414)
    - Le Sueur, Meridel, undated (Box 149, Folder 2415)
    - Levitan, Elsie, undated (Box 149, Folder 2416)
    - Levy, D. A., 1967, undated (Box 149, Folder 2417)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, 1967, undated (Box 149, Folder 2418)
    - Lindbloom, Nancy, undated (Box 149, Folder 2419)
    - Lindeman, Jack, 1958-1963, undated (Box 149, Folder 2420)
    - Lindsay, Karen, 1959, undated (Box 149, Folder 2421)
    - Litinskiya, Lina, 1968 May 27 (Box 149, Folder 2422)
    - Lott, Shirley, undated (Box 149, Folder 2423)
    - Lourie, Dick. Includes Who Is Lowenfels? typescript and typescript photocopy drafts, undated (Box 150, Folder 2424-2431)
    - Lovejoy, Don, undated (Box 150, Folder 2432)
    - [Folder numbers not used] (Box 150, Folder 2433-2438)
    - Lowenfels, Lillian
      - "The Critical Views of James Russell Lowell", 1945 (Box 150, Folder 2439)
      - "Emerson and Abolition", 1946 (Box 150, Folder 2440)
      - "Mark Twain and the Human Race", 1946 (Box 151, Folder 2441)
      - "Translations of Nicolas Quillen, Victoriano Cremer, Autustin Millares, Blas de Otera, Salomon de la Selva," with Nan Braymer, and other translations, undated (Box 151, Folder 2442-2444)
    - Luksic, Luis, undated (Box 151, Folder 2445)
    - Lynch, Felicity, 1969-1970 (Box 151, Folder 2446)
    - Lyons, Bonnie, undated (Box 151, Folder 2447)
    - McCarrell, Stuart. Includes Choose Earth!, Cities of Dirt, Cities of Light, and Not from Olympus, 1964, undated (Box 151, Folder 2448-2450)
    - McCord, Howard, undated (Box 151, Folder 2451)
    - McGrath, Thomas. Includes Letter to an Imaginary Friend, Vol. 2, 1962-1966, undated (Box 151, Folder 2452-2453)
    - Macoll, Ewan, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 2454)
    - Major, Clarence, undated (Box 152, Folder 2455)
    - Major, Joseph, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 2456)
    - Mally, Louise, undated (Box 152, Folder 2457)
    - Maltz, Albert, undated (Box 152, Folder 2458)
    - Maroti, Lajos, undated (Box 152, Folder 2459)
    - Martinez, Carmen M., 1969 (Box 152, Folder 2460)
    - Melman, Laura, undated (Box 152, Folder 2461)
    - Melman, Manna, undated (Box 152, Folder 2462)
    - Menasche, Anne, undated (Box 152, Folder 2463)
    - Mendez, Maria, undated (Box 152, Folder 2464)
    - Merton, Thomas, undated (Box 152, Folder 2465)
    - Meyer, Christopher, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 2466)
    - Meyer, June, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 2467)
    - Meyers, Bert, undated (Box 152, Folder 2468)
    - Mezey, Robert, undated (Box 152, Folder 2469)
    - Miller, Brown, undated (Box 152, Folder 2470)
    - Millett, Martha, undated (Box 152, Folder 2471)
    - Mitchell, Adrian, undated (Box 152, Folder 2472)
    - Montoyan, Jose, undated (Box 152, Folder 2473)
    - Moore, Robert Nelson J., undated (Box 152, Folder 2474)
    - Moraff, Barbara, undated (Box 152, Folder 2475)
    - Naeve, Virginia, undated (Box 152, Folder 2476)
    - Nandy, Pritish, 1968 April 22 (Box 152, Folder 2477)
    - Nayman, Louis, undated (Box 152, Folder 2478)
    - Newman, Michael, 1968-1972, undated (Box 152, Folder 2479)
    - Nguyen, Ðình Thi, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 2480)
    - Niatum, Duane, 1971-1973 (Box 152, Folder 2481)
    - Nichol, B. P., undated (Box 152, Folder 2482)
    - Nicholas, Michael, undated (Box 152, Folder 2483)
    - Noboa, Julia, undated (Box 152, Folder 2484)
    - North, Joseph, undated (Box 152, Folder 2485)
    - Nozinsky, Michael, undated (Box 152, Folder 2486)
    - Oliver, Joan, undated (Box 152, Folder 2487)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, undated (Box 152, Folder 2488)
    - Oswald, Anne, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 2489)
    - Owen, Becky, undated (Box 152, Folder 2490)
    - Pacheco, Manuel, undated (Box 153, Folder 2491)
    - Pareja, Miguel Donose, undated (Box 153, Folder 2492)
    - Parsons, Howard, 1973 June 21 (Box 153, Folder 2492a)
    - Paul, Irene, undated (Box 153, Folder 2492b)
    - Pennington, Lee, 1967 (Box 153, Folder 2492c)
    - Percikow, Henri, 1968-1969 (Box 153, Folder 2493)
    - Pereira, Teresinka, undated (Box 153, Folder 2494)
    - Perlo, Ellen, 1976, undated (Box 153, Folder 2495)
    - Perpelitt, Manna, 1972, undated (Box 153, Folder 2496)
    - Perumbaco, Veronica, undated (Box 153, Folder 2497)
    - Peterfreund, Stuart, undated (Box 153, Folder 2498)
    - Peterson, Michael, 1975 November 3 (Box 153, Folder 2499)
    - Piercy, Marge, undated (Box 153, Folder 2500)
    - Planz, Alan, undated (Box 153, Folder 2501)
    - Poe, Lee, circa 1970 (Box 153, Folder 2502)
    - Pollak, Felix, undated (Box 153, Folder 2503)
    - Posner, David, undated (Box 153, Folder 2504)
    - Pousada, Alicia, undated (Box 153, Folder 2505)
    - Provost, George, undated (Box 153, Folder 2506)
    - R J S, undated (Box 153, Folder 2507)
    - Randall, Margaret. Includes In the Spirit of Che, undated (Box 153, Folder 2508-2511)
    - Raphael, Lennox, undated (Box 153, Folder 2512)
    - Raoul, Sigmond, undated (Box 153, Folder 2513)
    - Ray, David, undated (Box 153, Folder 2514)
    - Redmond, Eugene. Includes The Indigenous Black American Epic, 1969, undated (Box 154, Folder 2515-2516)
    - Reed, Ishmael, undated (Box 154, Folder 2517)
    - Revsin, Elsa, undated (Box 154, Folder 2518)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth, undated (Box 154, Folder 2519)
    - Reyes, Carlos, 1966 (Box 154, Folder 2520)
    - Rich, David, 1967, undated (Box 154, Folder 2521)
    - Richards, Ellenia, undated (Box 154, Folder 2522)
    - Richardson, Beulah, undated (Box 154, Folder 2523)
    - Ristau, Harland, undated (Box 154, Folder 2524)
    - Rivera, Diego, 1955 April 13 (Box 154, Folder 2525)
    - Robbins, Doren, 1975 December 26 (Box 154, Folder 2526)
    - Robinson, Earl, 1975 (Box 154, Folder 2527)
    - Rodeiro, Joyce Anne, undated (Box 154, Folder 2528)
    - Rosenbaum, Veryl, undated (Box 154, Folder 2529)
    - Round, Harold L., 1957 December 21 (Box 154, Folder 2530)
    - Russell, Norman H., undated (Box 154, Folder 2531)
    - St. John, Primus, undated (Box 154, Folder 2532)
    - Sanchez, Sonia, undated (Box 154, Folder 2533)
    - Schechter, Ruth Lisa, 1967-1975, undated (Box 154, Folder 2534)
    - Schevill, James, undated (Box 154, Folder 2535)
    - Schleifer, Marc, undated (Box 154, Folder 2536)
    - Schulman, Howard, undated (Box 154, Folder 2537)
    - Schurr, Bonnie, undated (Box 154, Folder 2538)
    - Schwartz, Barry, undated (Box 154, Folder 2539)
    - Schwerner, Armand, undated (Box 154, Folder 2540)
    - Scozzafava, undated (Box 154, Folder 2541)
    - Segal, Edith, undated (Box 154, Folder 2542)
    - Sellin, Eric, undated (Box 154, Folder 2543)
    - Sharpe, Jacqueline, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 2544)
    - Shaw, George Bernard, undated (Box 155, Folder 2545)
    - Sheehan, Thomas, 1968 June (Box 155, Folder 2546)
    - Sherman, Jane, 1968, undated (Box 155, Folder 2547)
    - Shoush, Tawani Wakawa, undated (Box 155, Folder 2548)
    - Shy, Clyde, Jr., 1964-1967, undated (Box 155, Folder 2549)
    - Silber, Irwin, undated (Box 155, Folder 2550)
    - Simoneau, Jean, undated (Box 155, Folder 2551)
    - Sinavsky, Andrei, 1968 (Box 155, Folder 2552)
    - Sitwell, Edith, undated (Box 155, Folder 2553)
    - Skratz, G. P., undated (Box 155, Folder 2554)
    - Slotnikoff, Will, 1967 September 17 (Box 155, Folder 2555)
    - Smith, D. V., undated (Box 155, Folder 2556)
    - Smith, Ray, undated (Box 155, Folder 2557)
    - Snyder, Gary, undated (Box 155, Folder 2558)
    - Sobsey, Cynthia, undated (Box 155, Folder 2559)
    - Speer, Laurel, undated (Box 155, Folder 2560)
    - Spellman, A. B., undated (Box 155, Folder 2561)
    - Spriggs, Edward S., undated (Box 155, Folder 2562)
    - Stafford, William, undated (Box 155, Folder 2563)
    - Stanchi, Hugo, 1968-1974, undated (Box 155, Folder 2564)
    - Steiner, Stan, undated (Box 155, Folder 2565)
    - Stevens, Peter, undated (Box 155, Folder 2566)
    - Stinus, Eric, undated (Box 155, Folder 2567)
    - Stone, Ed, undated (Box 155, Folder 2568)
    - Suhl, Yuri, undated (Box 155, Folder 2569)
    - Sutherland, Eufa Theodora, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 2570)
    - Sward, Robert, undated (Box 155, Folder 2571)
    - Swing, Sam, undated (Box 155, Folder 2572)
    - Tagliabue, John, undated (Box 155, Folder 2573)
    - Tavel, Ronald, undated (Box 155, Folder 2574)
    - Taylor, Kent, undated (Box 155, Folder 2575)
    - Taylor, Walter, undated (Box 155, Folder 2576)
    - Te Hanh, 1963-1966 (Box 155, Folder 2577)
    - Thanh Hai, undated (Box 155, Folder 2578)
    - Thomas, Don, undated (Box 155, Folder 2579)
    - Thompson, Beverly, 1968-1969, undated (Box 155, Folder 2580)
    - Thornton, Cheryl, undated (Box 155, Folder 2581)
    - Tichenor, G. H., undated (Box 155, Folder 2582)
    - To Huu, 1965 November 7 (Box 155, Folder 2583)
    - Tobias, Tonya, undated (Box 155, Folder 2584)
    - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 2585)
    - Triem, Eve, 1968 March (Box 155, Folder 2585a)
    - Truesdale, C. W., 1973 (Box 155, Folder 2586)
    - Trunzo, Russell, 1963-1965, undated (Box 155, Folder 2587)
    - Tumbleweed, undated (Box 155, Folder 2588)
    - Turner, Melvin, undated (Box 155, Folder 2589)
    - Tuten, Marvin L., Jr., undated (Box 155, Folder 2590)
    - Tyler, Parker, undated (Box 155, Folder 2591)
    - Tyler, Ralph, undated (Box 155, Folder 2592)
    - Ubiles, Joseph R., Jr., undated (Box 156, Folder 2593)
    - Urin, Victor, undated (Box 156, Folder 2594)
    - Urquhart, Irene, undated (Box 156, Folder 2595)
    - Vallejo, Cesar. Translations by Nan Braymer and Lillian Lowenfels, undated (Box 156, Folder 2596-2597)
    - Vallverdu, Francisco, undated (Box 156, Folder 2598)
    - Van Brunt, H. L., 1969 May (Box 156, Folder 2599)
    - Vega, V., undated (Box 156, Folder 2600)
    - Vu Cao, 1956 December (Box 156, Folder 2601)
    - Walsh, B. B., undated (Box 156, Folder 2602)
    - Wantling, William, 1961-1970, undated (Box 156, Folder 2603-2604)
    - Weatherly, Thomas E., undated (Box 156, Folder 2605)
    - Webb, John Edgar, undated (Box 156, Folder 2606)
    - Weeks, Ramona, 1971 December (Box 156, Folder 2607)
    - Weiner, Hannah, undated (Box 156, Folder 2608)
    - Weinman, Paul L., undated (Box 156, Folder 2609)
    - Weiss, Lenore, 1970-1976, undated (Box 156, Folder 2610)
    - Welsh, James, undated (Box 156, Folder 2611)
    - Westlake, Nancy, undated (Box 156, Folder 2612)
    - White Feather, Anna, 1972, undated (Box 156, Folder 2613)
    - Willard, Nancy, undated (Box 156, Folder 2614)
    - Williams, Jonathan, undated (Box 156, Folder 2615)
    - Williams, Sonny, undated (Box 156, Folder 2616)
    - Williamson, Mickey, undated (Box 156, Folder 2617)
    - Wills, Frank, undated (Box 156, Folder 2618)
    - Wilson, Julie, undated (Box 156, Folder 2619)
    - Wilson, Keith, undated (Box 156, Folder 2620)
    - Winston, John, undated (Box 156, Folder 2621)
    - Wright, Sarah, undated (Box 156, Folder 2622)
    - Xuan-Dieu, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 2623)
    - Yeargens, Karl, undated (Box 156, Folder 2624)
    - Young, Al, undated (Box 156, Folder 2625)
    - Young Bear, Ray Anthony, undated (Box 156, Folder 2626)
    - Youree, Gary, undated (Box 156, Folder 2627)
  - Writings by Unknown Authors, 1966-1974
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by title.
    - "Absurdist Review from 57th Street", undated (Box 157, Folder 2628)
    - "April 24 day of eastern revolutionaries...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2629)
    - "Berceuse pour Rosa Luxembourg", undated (Box 157, Folder 2630)
    - "The birds fly high...", undatred (Box 157, Folder 2631)
    - "Bob Brown's 1450-1950", undated (Box 157, Folder 2632)
    - "Calabash", 1970 (Box 157, Folder 2633)
    - "Changes in the weather", undated (Box 157, Folder 2634)
    - "Chant", undated (Box 157, Folder 2635)
    - "Chief Evergreen", undated (Box 157, Folder 2636)
    - "Chiffon scarves and alligator shoes", undated (Box 157, Folder 2637)
    - "The cowboy", undated (Box 157, Folder 2638)
    - "Day night...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2639)
    - "The Electric Chair", undated (Box 157, Folder 2640)
    - "Endings - 1", undated (Box 157, Folder 2641)
    - "Equal Time", undated (Box 157, Folder 2642)
    - "Fabled Bard of Seven Songs", undated (Box 157, Folder 2643)
    - "Frances", undated (Box 157, Folder 2644)
    - "From that day on", undated (Box 157, Folder 2645)
    - "The ghostdancers", undated (Box 157, Folder 2646)
    - "Ginsberg and the Beats", undated (Box 157, Folder 2647)
    - "Globe", 1968 (Box 157, Folder 2648)
    - "'H' death and the life of all of us", 1954 (Box 157, Folder 2649)
    - "Him of life", undated (Box 157, Folder 2650)
    - "Hiroshima", undated (Box 157, Folder 2651)
    - "An improvement on excursions", undated (Box 157, Folder 2652)
    - "Introduction to radio program broadcast October 18, 1967", 1967 October 18 (Box 157, Folder 2653)
    - "It's in the air on Sunday", 1972 (Box 157, Folder 2654)
    - "Jotamario", undated (Box 157, Folder 2655)
    - "Le Silence", undated (Box 157, Folder 2656)
    - "Let Freedom Wake Him", undated (Box 157, Folder 2657)
    - "Letter from Ben - Tre", 1962 (Box 157, Folder 2658)
    - "Letter to Walter Lowenfels", undated (Box 157, Folder 2659)
    - "The line of first thinking concedes its boundaries...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2660)
    - "Love Chills in Boys and Girls", undated (Box 157, Folder 2661)
    - "The magic pencil", undated (Box 157, Folder 2662)
    - "The memory goes first...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2663)
    - "Mistery", undated (Box 157, Folder 2664)
    - "Music Is", undated (Box 157, Folder 2665)
    - "Nancy Cunard: Brave Poet, Indomitable Rebel, 1896-1965", undated (Box 157, Folder 2666)
    - "Nightmare" and "The nobility", undated (Box 157, Folder 2667)
    - "No customers as a sharpshooter", undated (Box 157, Folder 2668)
    - "No point in pointing", undated (Box 157, Folder 2669)
    - "Nun", undated (Box 157, Folder 2670)
    - "Ode au pain", undated (Box 157, Folder 2671)
    - "Off Amsterdam", undated (Box 157, Folder 2672)
    - "An offering", undated (Box 157, Folder 2673)
    - The Old Skidroad and Other Poems, partial typescript, undated (Box 157, Folder 2674)
    - "On a jazz high", undated (Box 157, Folder 2675)
    - "On not dreaming (final)", undated (Box 157, Folder 2676)
    - "An open letter to 'Che Guevara'", 1967 June 28 (Box 157, Folder 2677)
    - "Over 3 billion sold", 1968 November 25 (Box 157, Folder 2678)
    - "Part I", undated (Box 157, Folder 2679)
    - "Pictures In the Blood", 1961 May 24 (Box 157, Folder 2680)
    - "The Pity", 1962 July 21 (Box 157, Folder 2681)
    - "Pluie", undated (Box 157, Folder 2682)
    - "Poems 1963-1965", undated (Box 157, Folder 2683)
    - "Pole Jump Psalm", 1970 (Box 157, Folder 2684)
    - "A Postcard", undated (Box 157, Folder 2685)
    - "The Rane", undated (Box 157, Folder 2686)
    - "S as in Susie Q Invades Our Garden", undated (Box 157, Folder 2687)
    - "Saetas (Arrows of Song)", 1966 July 10 (Box 157, Folder 2688)
    - "The Saint of Marquetalia", undated (Box 157, Folder 2689)
    - "The sky of my land is laughing...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2690)
    - "Sleepless windows face hard relief", undated (Box 157, Folder 2691)
    - "Slick Yellow Girl", undated (Box 157, Folder 2692)
    - "Smoke clearing to the east of Harlem...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2693)
    - "Snow", undated (Box 157, Folder 2694)
    - "There is no distance...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2695)
    - "This is to inform...", 1974 March 3 (Box 157, Folder 2696)
    - "2 Sides of a Reflection", undated (Box 157, Folder 2697)
    - "To Walter", undated (Box 157, Folder 2698)
    - "Walt Whitman; II", 1965 November 30 (Box 157, Folder 2699)
    - "Walter Lowenfels (1961)", undated (Box 157, Folder 2700)
    - "War crimes and individual responsibility: a legal memorandum", undated (Box 157, Folder 2701)
    - "The water like tight blue silk...", undated (Box 157, Folder 2702)
    - "Without the Light My Seoul Go's", undated (Box 157, Folder 2703)
    - Wiltwyck poems, undated (Box 157, Folder 2704)
    - Criticism of Walter Lowenfels by others, undated (Box 157, Folder 2705)
    - Love poems by four Russian women, translated by Lillian Lowenfels and Nan Braymer, undated (Box 157, Folder 2706)
    - Poems in Spanish, undated (Box 157, Folder 2707)
    - Untitled works, undated (Box 157, Folder 2708)
- Photographs, 1897-1975; Series IV; 0.65; (2 boxes)
  Photographs is organized into two subseries: Photographs of Lowenfels and Family and Photographs of Others and Places.
  The series contains black-and-white and color photographic prints of Walter Lowenfels, his family, friends, his home, and other subjects.
  - Photographs of Lowenfels and Family, 1897-1975
    - Lowenfels, Walter, 1897-1975, undated (Box 158, Folder 2709-2716)
    - Lowenfels, Walter and Lillian, 1966, 1971, undated (Box 158, Folder 2717)
    - Lowenfels, Walter with unidentified others, undated (Box 158, Folder 2718)
    - Lowenfels, Lillian, 1926-1971, undated (Box 158, Folder 2719)
    - Lowenfels family, 1926-1949, undated (Box 158, Folder 2720-2721)
  - Photographs of Others and Places, 1930-1971
    - Brand, Millen, 1965 (Box 159, Folder 2722)